[{
    "question" : "Road Transport Ministry signed MoU with which institution for Research and Development" ,
    "options" :{
    "option1" : "IIT Roorkee" ,
    "option2" : "NIT Warangal",
    "option3" : "Central Institute of Road Transport",
    "option4" : "IIT Chennai"
    },
    "correctoption" : "IIT Roorkee"
},
{
    "question" : "The government of which state has decided to establish Indias biggest multi-model logistics park?" ,
    "options" :{
    "option1" : "Maharashtra" ,
    "option2" : "Tamil Nadu",
    "option3" : "West Bengal",
    "option4" : "Gujrat"
    },
    "correctoption" : "Gujrat"
},
{
    "question" : "The <Union Budget> Mobile application has been developed by which institution?" ,
    "options" :{
    "option1" : "National Informatics Centre" ,
    "option2" : "Indian Computer Emergency Response Team",
    "option3" : "Department of Telecommunications",
    "option4" : "National Technical Research Organisation"
    },
    "correctoption" : "National Informatics Centre"
},
{
    "question" : "Vaccination against which disease was conducted recently as a National Vaccination Day?" ,
    "options" :{
    "option1" : "Hepatitis" ,
    "option2" : "Polio",
    "option3" : "Pneumonia",
    "option4" : "BCG"
    },
    "correctoption" : "Polio"
},
{
    "question" : "Who chairs the NITI Aayog’s Governing Council meeting?" ,
    "options" :{
    "option1" : "Finance Minister" ,
    "option2" : "Prime Minister",
    "option3" : "NITI Aayog CEO",
    "option4" : "Home Minister"
    },
    "correctoption" : "Prime Minister"
},
{
    "question" : "Which Indian company has signed an agreement with Norway’s Greenstat for setting up a Centre of excellence on hydrogen?",
    "options" :{
    "option1" : "Hindustan Petroleum" ,
    "option2" : "Indian Oil",
    "option3" : "NTPC",
    "option4" : "GAIL"
    },
    "correctoption" : "Indian Oil"
},
{
    "question" : "Where is the Indian Institute of Sugarcane Research (llSR) located?",
    "options" :{
    "option1" : "Varanasi" ,
    "option2" : "Lucknow",
    "option3" : "Chandigarh",
    "option4" : "Gurgaon"
    },
    "correctoption" : "Lucknow"
},
{
    "question" : "Who is the head of the experts advisory committee set up for the Startup India Seed Fund Scheme?",
    "options" :{
    "option1" : "Injeti Srinivas" ,
    "option2" : "Gita Gopinath",
    "option3" : "H K Mittal",
    "option4" : "S C Khuntia"
    },
    "correctoption" : "H K Mittal"
},
{
    "question" : "Which Union Ministry has chalked out a four-point strategy to handle the blockage at Suez Canal?",
    "options" :{
    "option1" : "Ministry of Petroleum" ,
    "option2" : "Ministry of Commerce and Industry",
    "option3" : "Ministry of Heavy Industries",
    "option4" : "Ministry of External Affairs"
    },
    "correctoption" : "Ministry of Commerce and Industry"
},
{
    "question" : "<SARTHAQ>, which was seen in the news recently, is an implementation plan related to which policy?" ,
    "options" :{
    "option1" : "Environment Impact Assessment" ,
    "option2" : "Public Sector Enterprises Policy",
    "option3" : "New Education Policy",
    "option4" : "Agriculture Laws"
    },
    "correctoption" : "New Education Policy"
}
]